<?xml version="1.0"?>
<info>
    <id>contacts</id>
    <name>Contacts</name>
    <summary>Manage your CardDAV contacts from a feature-rich web-interface</summary>
    <description>
Contacts is a user interface for ownCloud's CardDAV server. ownCloud Server comes with a CardDAV component that allows users to synchronize and backup their address books with ownCloud and across multiple devices.
It provides users with an alternative to proprietary contact synchronization services giving them back control over their data once more.

The Contacts application is an extension to ownCloud's CardDAV interface. It equips ownCloud with a feature-rich frontend for the CardDAV server component, supports multiple address books and empowers users to easily manage their contacts from a web interface for ownCloud.
Users may find the URL for device synchronization (to configure synchronization in iOS, Android or other CardDAV-capable applications) in the 'Settings' section on the bottom left inside the application (link symbol).
Furthermore users can share address books with other users or groups (read-only/editable) enabling to synchronize address books not only across devices but also across users.
In addition to managing synchronized contacts the application also offers a feature to import contacts from vCards (.vcf).</description>
    <licence>AGPL</licence>
    <author>Hendrik Leppelsack, Thomas Müller, Alexander Weidinger, Jan-Christoph Borchardt, Tom Needham</author>
    <version>1.5.2</version>
    <documentation>
    	<user>https://doc.owncloud.org/server/10.0/user_manual/pim/index.html</user>
    	<admin>https://doc.owncloud.org/server/10.0/admin_manual/configuration/server/occ_command.html?highlight=contacts#dav-commands</admin>
    	<developer>https://github.com/owncloud/contacts/blob/master/README.md</developer>
    </documentation>
    <category>productivity</category>
    <website>https://github.com/owncloud/contacts</website>
    <bugs>https://github.com/owncloud/contacts/issues</bugs>
    <repository type="git">https://github.com/owncloud/contacts.git</repository>
    <screenshot>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/owncloud/screenshots/760f2783b03fd26cbc920188b672f5f5efe548c0/contacts/contacts.png</screenshot>
    <dependencies>
        <owncloud min-version="9.0" max-version="10.0" />
    </dependencies>
</info>
